ODEREMI OLUSEGUN EMMANUEL [WEB DEVELOPER]

Igbobi estate, Agbede, Agric, Ikorodu, Lagos. P: 08179135620, 07068451186, 09053517821.

E: remi.emma04@gmail.com.

PERSONAL PROFILE

I completed a BSc degree in computer science from Lagos state university, Ojo. I completed my compulsory one year of service (NYSC), in Oyo State, Ibadan North-east Local government precisely, where I was the President of my CDS group. I am an energetic and imaginative young web developer who is able to work alongside other talented IT professionals in creating websites to the very highest standards.

CERTIFICATIONS

•	Udemy Course	2019
	Certificate of Completion [Frontend Development (React)]	
•	Institute for Development Research	2019
	Certificate of Graduate Internship in International development	
•	Udemy Course	2019
	Certificate of Completion [JavaScript Boot-camp]	
•	Udemy Course	2019
	Certificate of Completion [Web developer Boot-camp]	
•	Par Avion Aviation Institute	2017
	Certification on Airport and Airline Management	
•	NIIT Nigeria	2016
	Certification on Web Development.	
•	IBM	2015
	Big Data Specialist with IBM Big-insights V2.1	
•	Omertag Plaza, Lagos	2009
	Certification on Desktop Publishing.	

PERSONAL SKILLS

Ability to work successfully as part of a team.

- Team work is a huge part of my person. Also, with my knowledge of software engineering, I learnt that projects have to be divided among several professionals, for optimal results.
- I love to take up challenges, and produce results.
- Can comfortably work under pressure.
- Always ready to learn new things.
- Good Communication Skills.
- Currently have a web app up and running online.

TECHNICAL SKILL SET

HTML	Scratch	Oracle
CSS	MySql	Heroku
NodeJS	Python	MongoDB

JavaScript Java ReactJS

PostgreSQL

EXPERIENCE

SIWES Training

For my compulsory siwes training, during my course of study in the university, I worked with the HOD of my department, Prof. Benjamin Aribisala. We worked on a project called; Segmentation of White Matter Hyper-intensities. I learnt to use computer software to determine and segment Lesions from brain images.

National Service

I was posted to a school where I teach JSS 3 classes, computer studies. There I learnt to work seamlessly with persons of all ages. I got to inspire my students, and show them just how wonderful life has gotten, because of the advent of the Computer System. It was fulfilling for me, because I got to inspire young minds, doing a lot of practical so I can enhance their view of the technological world. I was the President of the Sanitation CDS group, I got to lead the corp members in keeping the local government area, clean.

Internship

After successful completion of an aviation course I undertook while I served in Oyo state, where I got the certificate of the best graduating student, I underwent a two (2) month Internship, at Aero Contractors Airline, which is located at Old domestic wing of the Muritala Mohammed Airport, Ikeja. I have been able to garner experience working in the Resourcing department of the Airline.

Fd	ucat	or
Lu	ucai	.01

Unique Friends College			
CC Hub Yaba: Relearn Weekend Club.	May 2018	_	June 2018
CC Hub Yaba: Relearn Weekend Club.	February 2018	_	March 2018
CC Hub Yaba: Relearn Summer of Code.	July 2017	-	August 2017

Computer and PHE Teacher

May 2018 July 2018

Co Creation Hub

Mac Arthur Educator August 2018 February 2019 March 2019. Safe Online by Facebook November 2018 –

Adcem Healthcare

IT/Maintenance Officer July 2019 February 2020

Starfield College

ICT Instructor February 2020 till date

HOBBIES

- Coding: I love challenging myself to learn new things. I have knowledge in Web development, Python, Java, as well as Graphics designing.
- I love reading books, polishing my English is quite important to me.
- I relax with movies.
- I am also a gamer, with the hope of developing my own game eventually.
- I am a music lover.

EDUCATION SUMMARY

National Youth Service Corps N.Y.S.C Certificate.	2016 - 2017
Lagos State University, Ojo. Lagos state. BSc in Computer Science (CGPA 3.90/5).	2012 – 2015
Lagos State University, Ojo. LASU Foundation Programme (LFP), Transited. Lagos state.	2011 - 2012
Government Senior College, Ketu, Epe. Lagos state. West African Senior Secondary Certificate Examination (WAEC) certificate. National Examination Council (NECO) certificate.	2005 – 2008
Government Junior College, Ketu, Epe. Lagos state. West African Junior Secondary Certificate Examination.	2002 – 2005
Evergreen Royal Private School, Onike Yaba. Lagos state. Primary School Leaving Certificate.	1996 – 2002

REFEREES

Professor Benjamin Aribisala,

HOD, Computer Science Department, Lagos State University.

E: Benjamin.aribisala@gmail.com

Mr Adeokun Adeola,

Marketing Manager, Dangote group. P: 09058493297